roulettebotplus.com 2012-12-27

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy details how roulettebotplus.com compiles, uses, and protects any information that you provide us with while using our website.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should you be asked to provide certain information through which you may be identified, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

All data transmitted to us,  including names, addresses, contact information, postcode, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, interests, or habits,  will be used solely for processing downloads, or when a form is filled out. Your data will not be passed along to third parties.

To circumvent any unauthorized access we implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, or access your personal information. These security measures include password protected directories and databases to secure your information, Secure Sockets Layered (SSL) technology to ensure that your information is completely encrypted when sent across the Internet, or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

Your visit on roulettebotplus.com includes information pertaining to accessibility (date, time, viewed page) which can be saved on our server. This data is not part of the person-related data but is made anonymously. Examples include user’s Internet provider, type of Internet browser, etc.

We gather this information to better understand user needs, and to provide users with the best possible service. This data is used exclusively for statistical purposes so we can determine the best course of action needed to further improve on our offer to users, and to improve the overall user experience and satisfaction with our site.

You may request details pertaining to your personal information which we may hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. You as a user have a right to obtain this information free of charge, and if necessary a right to edit, lock, or delete this data.

We use cookies to identify which pages are visited and used by our users. A cookie is a small file which requests permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic. Thus the web application can tailor its operations to better fit your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering information about your personal preferences.

In general cookies are used as a tool to help us provide you with a better website. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies, and we do not have any control over these or any other websites. You should remember to exercise caution and to look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

We may periodically decide to send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which may be of some interest to you by using the email address which you have provided us with.

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information. If you have previously agreed to let us use your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us of your intentions.

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

This policy is effective as of May 1, 2011. roulettebotplus.com may decide to change this policy from time to time by updating this page. As such, you should monitor this page occasionally to ensure that you are satisfied with any and all changes.
